nomadix.com 2010-11-22

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy 

Introduction  
What information does Nomadix collect?  
What is this information used for?  
With whom is this information shared?  
What access do you have to information you provide?  
Security measures  
Disclaimer of responsibility for privacy policy and content at linked sites  
Use of information from third-parties  
This is not a children's web site  
Changes in these policies and practices  
More information

**Introduction**  
Nomadix respects your privacy. We make use of any personal information that you provide to us for the purpose of serving you better. We have created this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to demonstrate our firm commitment to online privacy. This “Notice of Privacy Policy” discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the Nomadix website which includes nomadix.com.This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to Nomadix and that Nomadix maintains electronically, whether you provide the information through nomadix.com or through other means. Additionally, this Privacy Policy applies to any personal information obtained from your use of the Nomadix website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that you may provide to third parties; for example, other sites linked to the Nomadix website. You should contact such third parties directly to determine their respective privacy policies. As used herein, the terms “Nomadix” “we,” “our” and “its” when referring to Nomadix are used only for convenience and are not intended to be an accurate description of ownership, operation or corporate/legal relationships.

**What information does Nomadix collect?  **  
If you are a customer of Nomadix, we collect and maintain a variety of personal information about you and your company. This information may be collected through nomadix.com or through paper forms submitted by you. Examples of this information include: 

  * your company name 
  * your location 
  * your type of business 
  * your industry 
  * your contact information including your first and last name, contact email address and contact phone 

Depending on the use that you make of the Nomadix website, we may also collect your NSE’s network Internet Protocol (IP) Address, information about your gateway(s) including NSE ID, serial number, Administrator’s user name, Administrator’s password, installed firmware version, and configuration settings (e.g. is the IPsec feature enabled, is the Multiple SSID feature enabled, and which ports are blocked).  Nomadix may store and analyze log files from user sessions. Nomadix may use cookies (alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser) to log you in to certain areas of our website.

**What is this information used for?**  
We use your information in the course of your customer relationship with Nomadix. Among other things, we use this information to provide you with the services available on Nomadix.com. For example, we allow you to edit and update information online. We also use your information for other things which may include, but are not limited to, the following:

  * **Contacting You**  
Nomadix uses your personally identifiable contact information to communicate with you in the course of your customer relationship. Such information includes your first and last name, contact phone number, and contact email address. 
  * **Use of IP Address** _  
_ IP addresses are numbers that are automatically assigned to your NSE’s network computer, and, if associated with other individually identifiable information, could be considered personal information. We use your IP address to upgrade your NSE’s firmware. 
  * **Use of NSE Administrator User Name and Password**  
Nomadix uses your NSE Administrator’s User Name and Password to log into your NSE and upgrade your firmware. We recommend you change your password after the upgrade is complete. 

**With whom is this information shared?**  
Nomadix shares your information only as described below. Nomadix does not sell or share your information with third parties.

  * **Business Transfers** _  
_ Information regarding customers is shared with MagiNet, our parent company as they may assist us in supporting our customers. 

**What access do you have to information you provide?**  
You can view and update the information you provide to us prior to sending your firmware upgrade request to Nomadix.

**Security measures**  
While the use of the Nomadix website does not involve collection of personal confidential information about you, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to Nomadix.

**Disclaimer of responsibility for privacy policy and content at linked sites**  
The Nomadix website may provide you with links to other websites. We are not responsible for those sites and cannot control the use of information that you submit once you reach those sites, nor can we control the content of what is offered on those sites or on links from those sites. You should contact such third-party websites directly to determine their privacy policies.

**Use of information from third parties**  
We do not use information about you provided to us by third parties.

**This is not a children’s website**  
Nomadix does not knowingly solicit data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children.

**Changes in these policies and practices**  
Nomadix reserves the right to change its privacy policies and practices periodically, without providing individual notice, by updating this Privacy Policy notice. **This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 12, 2006**. You agree that it is your responsibility to monitor such updates and that your continued use of the Nomadix website after such revisions have been made constitutes your full acceptance of such revised terms and conditions.

**More Information**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please write to:

Nomadix  
Attn: Privacy Policy Inquiry  
30851 Agoura Road  
Suite 102  
Agoura Hills, CA 91301  
Telephone: 818-597-1500   
Email address: [privacypolicy@nomadix.com](mailto:privacypolicy@nomadix.com)
